<resources>


    <!--Other-->
    <string name="my_music">My Music</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorite Music</string>
    <string name="audio_books">Audio Books</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="album">Album</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="artist">Artist</string>
    <string name="length">Length</string>
    <string name="audio_book">Audio Book</string>
    <string name="play_button_pressed">Play Button Pressed</string>
    <string name="pause_button_pressed">Pause Button Pressed</string>
    <string name="forward_button_pressed">Forward Button Pressed</string>
    <string name="rewind_button_pressed">Rewind Button Pressed</string>


    <!--Error -->
    <string name="error_collection_full">Error: No space for more titles.</string>

    <!--InfoText-->
    <string name="info_text_main">This is the Home Layout after starting the app. The software checks the
    root folder of the app about music files, audio books and play lists of the user. The user can
    see his folders and could touch on it to get into it..</string>

    <string name="info_text_audio_books">Here we can see the content of a directory called Audio
    Books. The user can see his audio books and can play a audio book with a touch the play button.
    Further he can touch on the info button on the right hand side of the play button.
    This button will show info about the audio book.</string>

    <string name="info_text_play_list">Here we can see the content of a directory called My Music.
    The user can see his songs and can play a song with a touch the play button.
    Further he can touch on the info button on the right hand side of the play button.
    This button will show info about the song.</string>

    <string name="info_text_song_play">This is the Play Screen of the app. The user can see the cover,
    the Title, the Artist and the Length of the chosen song. With a click on the pause button, the
    song will pause, forward will go fast forward, rewind fast back. Play will play after Pause.</string>

    <string name="info_text_audio_book_play">This is the Play Screen of the app. The user can see the cover,
    the Title, the Author and the Length of the chosen audio book. With a click on the pause button, the
    book will pause, forward will go fast forward, rewind fast back. Play will play after Pause.</string>

    <string name="info_text_title_info">This is the Info Screen of the app. Here the user
    can see all details of his chosen title. Cover, Album, Author/Artist, Length and Title.</string>




</resources>
