<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide for Graz</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="city_name">Graz</string>
    <string name="adress">Address:</string>
    <string name="telephone">Telephone:</string>
    <string name="email">Email:</string>
    <string name="website">Website:</string>
    <string name="no_email_address">---</string>
    <string name="no_website">---</string>
    <string name="no_telephone">---</string>

    <!-- FOOD-->
    <!-- Aiola Upstairs Restaurant-->
    <string name="aiola_upstairs_name">Aiola Upstairs</string>
    <string name="aiola_telephone">+43/316/8181797</string>
    <string name="aiola_email">upstairs@aiola.at</string>
    <string name="aiola_address">Schlossberg 2</string>
    <string name="aiola_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="aiola_website">http://upstairs.aiola.at</string>
    <string name="aiola_description">Above the city, delight knows no bounds! And this from morning
        till evening too. Via the ‘Lift im Berg’ elevator you’re up there in a trice and can start
        the day with a latte in the morning sunshine. The glass walls, surrounding the tastefully
        designed aiola upstairs on Schlossberg hill, vanish underground when the weather is fine.
        Enchanting dining al fresco in the evening by moon and candle light. The aiola upstairs in
        Graz offers everything you could wish for: breakfast, lunch and dinner.</string>

    <!--Baristas Coffeeshop-->
    <string name="barista_names">Barista\'s</string>
    <string name="baristas_telephone">+43/316/225467</string>
    <string name="baristas_email">upstairs@aiola.at</string>
    <string name="baristas_address">Franziskanerplatz 4-5</string>
    <string name="baristas_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="baristas_website">www.baristas.at</string>
    <string name="baristas_description">Coffee lovers have a huge selection of warm and cold coffee
        variations, smoothies and milkshakes. For the peckish there\’s a big choice of bagels and
        sweet temptations like brownies, muffins and cookies as well as various kinds of cheesecake,
        carrot cake and apple pie. Barrista\'s offers a big choice of breakfast specialities - at
        Eggenberg, University and Music &amp; Art as well as Tummelplatz square till 3pm, and
        downtown at Franziskanerplatz square till 11pm.</string>

    <!--Burger Factory-->
    <string name="burger_factory_name">Burger Factory</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_telephone">+43/316/710172</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_email">office@burger-factory.at</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_address">Feuerbachgasse 24</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_website">www.burger-factory.at</string>
    <string name="burger_factory_description">The team at the Burger Factory now brings the American way
        of life into the Styrian capital, with burgers made using fresh local ingredients.
        The patties, cut fries, sauces and buns are all home-made. Try their classic, cheese,
        buffalo or veggie burgers!</string>

    <!--Bur-->
    <string name="bur_name">Bur</string>
    <string name="bur_telephone">+43/660/4394368</string>
    <string name="bur_email">office@bur-graz.at</string>
    <string name="bur_address">Alte Poststraße 460–462</string>
    <string name="bur_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="bur_website">www.burger-factory.at</string>
    <string name="bur_description">BUR is a bar, restaurant and club - and one of the
        hottest establishments Styria has to offer. Merging the traditional with the contemporary,
        BUR offers a party atmosphere and serves exquisite cocktails and much more. Ideal for
        events of any kind.</string>


    <!--SIGHTS-->
    <!--Schlossberg-->
    <string name="schlossberg_name">Schlossberg</string>
    <string name="schlossberg_address">Am Schlossberg</string>
    <string name="schlossberg_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="schlossberg_description">In the city and on the summit – certainly no
        contradiction in Graz. The river, unique historic city centre and, right in the middle,
        a mountain. The Schlossberg hill of Graz is at once a natural spectacle, central recreation
        area and vantage point. It takes but a short time to ascend and enjoy the beautiful views
        of Graz and surroundings. The city owes its name to the castle, which was built more than
        1000 years ago on this hill. From the Slavonic word Gradec for ‘little castle’ later
        emerged Graz.</string>

    <!--Island in The Mur-->
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_names">Island in the Mur</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_telephone">+43/316/822660</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_email">murinsel@tele2.at</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_address">Lendkai 19</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_website">www.murinselgraz.at</string>
    <string name="island_in_the_mur_description">Island or boat? It isn’t easy to tell with this
        extravagant steel construction by US-American artist Vito Acconci. The Island in the Mur,
        Graz was commissioned as part of the city’s role as Capital of Culture in 2003. What is
        clear is its function as a link between river and city, a wonderful place to drink coffee
        or enjoy a cocktail. With the river Mur swirling cheerfully by on both left and right
        sides, from the Murinsel you can appreciate a completely new perspective of the city
        of Graz.</string>

    <!--Kunsthaus Graz-->
    <string name="kunsthaus_name">Kunsthaus Graz</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_telephone">+43/316/8017–9200</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_email">kunsthausgraz@museum-joanneum.at</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_address">Lendkai 1</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_website">www.kunsthausgraz.at</string>
    <string name="kunsthaus_description">Wonder, enthusiasm, incredulity. The spectacular architecture of
        Graz Kunsthaus leaves nobody cold. Whilst it\’s not common for existing, traditional urban
        buildings to sit so perfectly next to breathtaking new architecture, with the setting of
        this museum of contemporary art in Graz it’s definitely the case. The Kunsthaus floats
        like a mysterious blue balloon between the roofs of the historic city centre. Named
        friendly alien by its creators, its fascinating magic draws visitors in.</string>

    <!--Eggenberg Palace-->
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_name">Eggenberg Palace</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_telephone">+43/316/8017–9560</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_email">eggenberg@museum-joanneum.at</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_address">Eggenberger Allee 90</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_website">museum-joanneum.at/de/eggenberg_schloss</string>
    <string name="eggenberg_palace_description">The universe is in Graz! It\’s no joke, but rather a wonderful
        example of harmonious architectural skill: Eggenberg Palace on the edge of the city centre.
        Set within a beautiful park is the main palace, which was laid out as an architectural
        allegory of the universe. The building represents a precisely calculated cosmos. It was
        commissioned by Prince Hans Ulrich von Eggenberg from the year 1625 to embody his wish for
        a harmonious structure, reacting to the chaos of the 16th century.</string>


    <!--PARKS-->
    <!--Stadtpark-->
    <string name="stadtpark_name">Stadtpark</string>
    <string name="stadtpark_address">Stadtpark 1</string>
    <string name="stadtpark_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="stadtpark_description">Who doesn\’t know the “Staedtchen Drumherum”
        (The Little Town all around) by Mira Lobe? This is what you see, when you look at Graz
        Stadtpark grounds from above. A green island in the middle of the roofscape of Unesco world
        cultural heritage. During the day kids would storm the enormous playground next to
        strollers and bon vivants settling comfortably underneath chestnut trees and on park
        benches. In the afternoon and evening, Graz people love to meet here for an after-business
        drink at one of the cafés. And should you happen to have some nuts in your pocket, you’ll
        be able to make new friends amongst the park inhabitants – the local squirrels.</string>

    <!--Burggarten-->
    <string name="burggarten_names">Burggarten</string>
    <string name="burggarten_address">Hofgasse 15</string>
    <string name="burggarten_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="burggarten_description">A romantic picnic in the middle of town.
        Burggarten park in Graz is a magical place for a plan like that. This picturesque park is
        almost a secret spot, because who would have thought that, behind the seat of the regional
        government above Stadtpark, so much romance is to be found? Another highlight here is the
        former Orangerie which, following loving and extensive refurbishment, is now open for
        events and receptions of all kinds.</string>

    <!-->Botanical Garden-->
    <string name="botanical_garden_name">Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_telephone">+43/316/380–5651</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_email">jonathan.wilfling@uni-graz.at</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_address">Holtigasse 6</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_website">www.garten.uni-graz.at</string>
    <string name="botanical_garden_description">A trip up the garden path is a welcome diversion when it\’s
        taking you to the Botanical Gardens at the Institute of Botany. The exotic architectural
        design of the greenhouses is a perfect reflection of the extraordinary wealth of plants
        to be found here – including three climate zones and a diversity of well known and lesser
        known specimens.</string>

    <!--Hilmteich-->
    <string name="hilmteich_name">Hilmteich</string>
    <string name="hilmteich_address">Hilmteichstraße 70</string>
    <string name="hilmteich_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="hilmteich_website">www.holding-graz.at/freizeit/hilmteich.html</string>
    <string name="hilmteich_description">What are your favourite activities? A romantic boat
        trip followed by a picnic? Some cool climbing experience at Klettererlebnis im
        Erlebnispark? Do you prefer a gentle walk or would you like to explore forest tracks in
        running gear? Both Hilmteich lake and the adjoining Leechwald forest offer all sorts of
        activities. Your individual relaxation and recreation is guaranteed – at the very latest
        when stopping in at Purberg restaurant.</string>


    <!-- HOTELS-->
    <!--Das Weitzer-->
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_name">Das Weitzer</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_telephone">+43/316/703–0</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_email">hotel@weitzer.com</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_address">Grieskai 12–16</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_website">www.hotelweitzer.com</string>
    <string name="hotel_weitzer_description">“Das Weitzer” is located in the city centre, just 5
        minutes walk from the main square. All you would expect and more: 204 newly designed
        rooms, the beautiful “Kingdom of Angels” breakfast room, regional produce including a
        wine and gift shop in the “Steirer” restaurant, a florist, the “Café Weitzer” traditional
        coffee house, together with a spa including sauna, steam room and work-out equipment. A
        nice detail: guests can rent bicycles. Free WLAN throughout the building. </string>

    <!--Hotel Daniel-->
    <string name="hotel_daniel_names">Hotel Daniel</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_telephone">+43/316/711080</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_email">hellograz@hoteldaniel.com</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_address">Europaplatz 1</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_postcode">8020 Graz</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_website">www.hoteldaniel.at</string>
    <string name="hotel_daniel_description">"Urban Stay – Smart Luxury” is the credo at the
        Daniel – tasteful minimalism and service that focuses on an uncomplicated sense of
        well being. 108 rooms with free WLAN, air conditioning and rain shower. The best breakfast
        in town every morning. 10 minutes’ walk into the city centre, bus and tram stops right in
        front of the hotel. Or you can explore on the Vespas and bike boards available from the
        in-house fleet.</string>

    <!--Parkhotel Graz-->
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_name">Parkhotel Graz</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_telephone">+43/316/3620–0</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_email">office@parkhotel-graz.at</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_address">Leonhardstraße 8</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_postcode">8010 Graz</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_website">www.parkhotel-graz.at</string>
    <string name="parkhotel_graz_description">Centrally located yet in a tranquil environment the
        Parkhotel Graz is the ideal choice for visitors of the Styrian capital. Business travellers
        will find the convenience of the hotel´s own restaurant “Florian” as well as the cosy
        cocktail bar. The hotel further boasts its own little Spa and various seminar rooms which
        provide a quiet work environment – all you can wish for. On the other side this 4 Star
        Superior hotel is the ideal home away from home for people looking for a place to stay at
        during a romantic getaway.</string>

    <!--Hotel Paradies-->
    <string name="hotel_paradies_name">Hotel Paradies</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_telephone">+43/316/282156</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_email">info@hotelpardies.at</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_address">Straßegangerstraße 380b</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_postcode">8054 Graz</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_website">www.hotelparadies.at</string>
    <string name="hotel_paradies_description">Welcome to paradise! At the foot of Schloss St. Martin, with
        excellent public transport connections to the centre of Graz, is the **** "Paradies".
        The hotel indulges its guests with international cuisine in its restaurant and invites them
        to relax on comfortable terraces enjoying a view of the lush landscape. Those keen on
        sports will find a gym, tennis courts, outdoor pool, sauna and steam bath.</string>

</resources>
